Finding Aid for Museum of Art (University of Michigan) records, 1946-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Exhibition Files, 1946-2003
  - 1978-1979
    - "Ludwig Meidner: An Expressionist Master (Drawings and Prints from the D. Thomas Bergen Collection; Paintings from the Marvin and Janet Fishman Collection),", October 20-November 19, 1978 (Box 8)
      (includes correspondence with Mr. Bergen)
    - Islamic exhibition (ceramics and metalworks), November 1978-August 1979 (Box 8)
    - Callot mini-show, November 27-December 22, 1978 (Box 8)
    - "Zenga and Nanga: Paintings by Japanese Monks and Scholars [from the Collection of Dr. and Mrs. Kurt A. Gitter],", November 26, 1978-January 8, 1979 (Box 8)
      (New Orleans Museum of Art)
    - Art faculty exhibition, January 5-February 4, 1979 (Box 8)
    - "Close Observation: Selected Oil Sketches by Frederic E. Church,", March 17-April 29, 1979 (Box 8)
    - "John Mentresor in America: Eighteenth Century Military Maps,", April 19-May 20, 1979 (Box 8)
      (UMMA & William L. Clements Library)
    - "The Art of Russia 1800-1850,", February 16-March 16, 1979 (Box 8)
      (University of Minnesota Gallery with the Committee on Institutional Cooperation and the Ministry of Culture of USSR)
  - 1979-1980
    - Schedule (Box 8)
    - "Image and Life: 50,000 Years of Japanese Prehistory,", August 26-November 11, 1979 (Box 8)
      (University of Columbia, Museum of Anthropology)
    - "The Inuit Print,", September 16-October 14, 1979 (Box 8)
      (Canadian National Museum of Man and the Canadian Department of Indian & Northern Affairs)
      (in conjunction with "Inuit Sculpture from the Collection of Mr. & Mrs. Eugene B. Power")
    - "16th and 17th Century Drawings,", October 13-December 9, 1979 (Box 8)
    - Photography-Survey for class, November-December 1979 (Box 8)
    - Decorative arts exhibition mini-exhibit, Winter semester, 1979-1980 (Box 8)
    - "The Crisis of Impressionism, 1878-1882,", November 2, 1979-January 6, 1980 (Box 8)
    - "Eighteenth-Century Prints and Drawings,", January 12-March 9, 1980 (Box 8)
      (part of "Eighteenth-Century Semester," Winter 1980, Literature, Science & the Arts and School of Music)
    - "Ceramics in the Collections of the University of Michigan,", February 1-March 16, 1980 (Box 8)
    - "Dutch Prints & Drawings from the Collection of the UMMA,", March 8-May 4, 1980 (Box 8)
    - "American Photographs: Gifts from the Collection of Marvin Felheim,", March 14-May 19, 1980 (Box 8)
    - "Fifteen Photographs: A Purchase Exhibition,", March 24-April 12, 1980 (Box 8)
    - "Helen Frankenthaler: Works of the Seventies,", April 4-May 11, 1980 (Box 8)
      (Saginaw Art Museum)
    - "Inside and Beyond: Photographs by Joanne Leonard,", May 30-July 31, 1980 (Box 8)
      (Laguna Gloria Art Museum)
      (alumna and subsequent professor of UM School of Art)
    - "Recent Acquisitions,", May 30-July 31, 1980 (Box 8)
  - 1980-1981
    - Schedule (Box 8)
    - "Eugène Atget: Twenty Photographs,", August 1-October 31, 1980 (Box 8)
    - "Paris and the American Avant-Garde: 1900-1925,", September 19-November 2, 1980 (Box 8)
      (Museum Practice Program)
    - "Selections from the Collection of The Alex Hillman Family Foundation,", September 19-December 15, 1980 (Box 8)
    - "Ansel Adams: Portfolio VI," November 15,1980-, January 9, 1981 (Box 8)
    - "From the Winston-Malbin Collection: Various Media and Formats,", November 29, 1980-February 1, 1981 (Box 8)
      (Vassar College Art Gallery)
    - "Tibetan Tankas from Dr. Koelz Collection,", October 17-December 24, 1980 (Box 8)
    - "Landscape Drawings: An Artist's Choice [Al Mullen: Selected Drawings],", January 2-February 15, 1981 (Box 8)
    - "Three Master Etchers: Tissot, Buhot, Bracquemond," February 18-[May ?], 1981 (Box 8)
    - "Michigan Artists 1980/1981 (Southeast Region)," March 6-April 15, 1981 (Box 8)
    - "James Leacock: Clay and Water," April-[October 14], 1981 (Box 8)
  - 1981-1982
    - Schedule (Box 8)
    - "African Images: Art and Ornament,", April 3-August 9, 1981 (Box 8)
    - "The Meeting of Two Worlds: The Crusades and the Mediterranean Context,", May 9-September 27, 1981 (Box 8)
    - Picasso on paper, May 16-October 4, 1981 (Box 8)
    - "Roma Resurgens: Papal Medals from the Age of the Baroque,", August 29-October 11, 1981 (Box 8)
    - "Works from the Collection of Jean Paul Slusser,", October 3-November 1, 1981 (Box 8)
    - "20th Century Russian Prints,", November 10-December 23, 1981 (Box 8)
    - Reinstallation of the museum, January 1982 (Box 9)
    - "School of Art Faculty: A Rackham Grant Exhibition 1982,", January 9-February 28, 1982 (Box 9)
    - "Dutch Art,", February 28-May 9, 1982 (Box 9)
    - "Frank Stella,", March 19-April 11, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Gentileschi paintings (Detroit Institute of the Arts), February 8-March 19, 1982 (Box 9)
    - "Margaret Watson Parker: A Collector's Legacy,", March 20-April 25, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Exhibition in basement stairwell cases (Decorative arts), [May 7-?, 1981] (Box 9)
  - 1982-1983
    - Schedule (Box 9)
    - "Italian Prints and Drawings,", May 7-June 13, 1982 (Box 9)
    - "Leonardo's Return to Vinci,", May 8-June 13, 1982 (Box 9)
      (University Art Museum, Berkeley and Italian Cultural Institute of San Francisco)
    - "Street Photography,", July 10-August 22, 1982 (Box 9)
    - "Quilts and Ceramics,", July 10-August 22, 1982 (Box 9)
    - "Frank Stella: Prints 1967-1982,", September 25-November 21, 1982 (Box 9)
      (includes correspondence with the artist, 3 audiocassettes of artist interviews, and installation slides)
    - "Gifts from University of Michigan Alumni,", September 25, 1982-January 7, 1983 (Box 9)
    - "Medieval and Renaissance Ceramics from the Kassebaum Collection,", November 12, 1982-January 13, 1983 (Box 9)
      (Spencer Art Museum, University of Kansas)
    - "Nudes from Michigan Collections,", December 10, 1982-February 27, 1983 (Box 9)
    - "Pre-Columbian Art,", January 5-June 6, 1983 (Box 9)
    - "An Armenian Treasury in Michigan,", February 26-April 10, 1983 (Box 9)
    - "Jan Beekman,", March 6-April 10, 1983 (Box 9)
    - "Forest, Prairie, and Plains: Native American Art from the Chandler/Pohrt Collection,", March 18-May 22, 1983 (Box 9)
    - "Howard Bond Photographs,", May 5-June 5, 1983 (Box 9)
    - "Heart Mountains and Human Ways: Japanese Landscape and Figure Painting" (UMMA), [, July-October 1983 (Box 9)
      (Museum of Fine Arts, Houston)
    - "Kyoto Metal: An Exhibition of Contemporary Japanese Art Metalwork,", May 14-June 26, 1983 (Box 9)
      (North Texas State University)
    - "Austrian and German Expressionist Drawings from a Private Collection,", June 11-August 11, 1983 (Box 9)
  - 1983-1984
    - Schedule (Box 9)
    - "Jean-Louis Forain: Artist, Realist, Humanist,", June 11-July 24, 1983 (Box 9)
    - "Tiffany Glass from the Permanent Collection,", July 16-September 1983 (Box 9)
    - "John Randolph Carter,", August 15-September 18, 1983 (Box 9)
      (includes correspondence with the artist and installation photographs)
    - "Gerome Kamrowski: A Retrospective Exhibition,", August 30-October 16, 1983 (Box 9)
      (includes transcripts of artist interview and installation slides)
    - "Prints from the Reformation and Counter-Reformation Period,", September 9-October 9, 1983 (Box 9)
    - "Klipper/Rosenberg: Space, Exploration, Definition,", September 23-October 23, 1983 (Box 9)
    - "The Artistic Revival of the Woodcut in France: 1850-1900,", November 4, 1983-January 4, 1984 (Box 9)
    - "[Reginald] Malcolmson: Visionary Architecture,", January 24-March 11, 1984 (Box 9)
    - "Trends and Traditions in Japanese Art,", March 23-June 10, 1984; 2 folders (Box 9)
      (includes teachers' packet)
    - "Victorian Medals,", Spring 1984 (Box 9)
  - 1984-1985
    - Schedule (Box 9)
    - "Ceramics from the Permanent Collections,", July-August 1984 (Box 9)
    - "Images of the Performing Arts: Music, Dance, and Theater,", July 1-August 15, 1984 (Box 9)
    - "Gus Foster Panoramic Photographs,", September 14-October 21, 1984 (Box 9)
    - "The Influence of Surrealism on American Art: Loans from the Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum,", September 28, 1984-June 16, 1985 (Box 9)
    - "African Art,", October-December 1984 (Box 9)
    - "Cyril Lixenberg: Design Projects,", October 19-November 18, 1984 (Box 9)
      (includes catalogues in German)
    - "Sculpture of Africa: Selections from a Private Collection,", November 2-December 23, 1984 (Box 9)
    - "In the Grand Manner: British Paintings and Prints from the Detroit Institute of Arts,", January 7-May 25, 1985 (Box 9)
    - "Jori Mazer Blackman: Mixed Devotion,", February 1-March 10, 1985 (Box 9)
    - "The World of Kameda Bosai,", February 15-March 31, 1985 (Box 9)
    - "Earth Magicians: Pottery from The Collections of the University of Michigan,", March 29-June 16, 1985 (Box 9)
      (includes docent training guide, children's exhibition guide and label copy)
    - "Views of Florence and Tuscany [by Giuseppe Zocchi 1711-1767]," April 22-?, 1985 (Box 9)
      (selected from collection of the Pierpont Morgan Library)
  - 1985-1986
    - Schedule (Box 9)
    - "Ten-Chi: Prints by Takeshi Takahara,", June 7-July 28, 1985 (Box 9)
    - "The Federal Art Project: American Prints from the 1930s in the Collection of the University of Michigan Museum of Art,", June 28-August 1985 (Box 9)
    - "Homage to Arnheim: Principles of Art and Visual Perception,", August 16-September 22, 1985 (Box 9)
    - "Al Mullen: A Drawing Retrospective,", August 30-October 19, 1985 (Box 9)
      (includes label copy)
    - "Pechstein to Penck: 20th Century German Art,", November 1985-January 1986 (Box 9)
    - "Photography from the Permanent Collection,", December 1985-January 1986 (Box 9)
    - "Forty Years at the UMMA: An Anniversary Exhibition,", January 24-March 29, 1986 (Box 9)
  - 1986-1987
    - Schedule (Box 10)
    - "The Rising of a New Moon: A Century of Tabwa Art,", April 18-July 27, 1986 (Box 10)
    - "Signs and Seats of Power,", April 21-July 28, 1986 (Box 10)
      (includes installation photographs and label copy)
    - "Albert Kahn: Architectural Studies,", September 5-October 26, 1986 (Box 10)
    - "Hispanic Cultural Objects," September 12-[October 15?], 1986 (Box 10)
    - "Paperworks: Dialogue-Interaction" (Frank Cassara), November 7-December 6, 1986 (Box 10)
    - "Latent Images: 10 Midwestern Photographers,", November 11-December 6, 1986 (Box 10)
      (Arts Midwest)
    - "Legacy of Metaphor: Photographs as Equivalent," [Winter 1987] (Box 10)
    - "Ramsay Stuart: Transitional Planes" (Ted Ramsay and Paul Stuart), January 16-March 1, 1987 (Box 10)
    - "Maggie Citrin", March-April 1987 (Box 10)
    - "Old Master Drawings: A Selection from the Permanent Collection,", March 16-April 20, 1987 (Box 10)
    - Southeast Asian Exhibition, March 31-August 31, 1987 (Box 10)
    - "From Seedtime to Harvest,", April 12-May 31, 1987 (Box 10)
    - "The Modern Figure in Motion,", May 1-June 7, 1987 (Box 10)
  - 1987-1988
    - Schedule (Box 10)
    - "Kawase Hasui and His Contemporaries: The Shin Hanga (New Print) Movement in Landscape Art,", June 16-August 2, 1987 (Box 10)
    - "Stories from China's Past: Han Dynasty Pictorial Tomb Reliefs and Archaeological Objects from Sichuan Province, People's Republic of China,", September 8-October 25, 1987 (Box 10)
      (Chinese Culture Center of San Francisco)
      (includes invitations)
    - "Set/Suit/Suite: Serial Imagery from Aldegrever to Warhol,", November 10-December 3, 1987 (Box 10)
    - "Shoowa Textiles,", December 18, 1987-February 7, 1988 (Box 10)
    - "Dream Keepers: A Celebration of Black Art,", February 2-28, 1988 (Box 10)
    - "Contemporary Inuit Drawings,", February 16-March 20, 1988 (Box 10)
      (Macdonald Stewart Art Centre)
  - 1988-1989
    - Schedule (Box 10)
    - "Mignonette Yin Cheng,", March 4-May 1, 1988 (Box 10)
    - "Rites of Spring: Passing Moments, Eternal Cycles,", April 8-May 30, 1988 (Box 10)
    - "Photo-collage,", May 13-June 30, 1988 (Box 10)
    - "Picasso Prints,", May 1988 (Box 10)
    - "Frederick Sommer,", May 10-June 26, 1988 (Box 10)
    - "As Good as Gold: A Celebration of Two Decades of Gifts by The Friends of The Museum of Art,", September 30-December 18, 1988 (Box 10)
    - "Unseen America: Small Oils from the Permanent Collection,", October 28, 1988-January 15, 1989 (Box 10)
      (includes label copy and photograph)
    - "[Elegance and Utility]" (Snuff Bottles/Netsukes from Bowdoin), July 15-October 16, 1988 (Box 10)
    - "Pure Elegance: A Decade of Asian Art Collecting at the UMMA,", January 20-March 19, 1989 (Box 10)
    - "Art in Flower,", March 28-April 30, 1989 (Box 10)
    - "All Creatures Great and Small,", March 31-May 21, 1989 (Box 10)
    - "Paradise Found,", April 11-June 11, 1989 (Box 10)
  - 1989-1990
    - Schedule (Box 10)
    - "Michigan Water Color Society 43rd Annual Exhibition,", June 6-August 6, 1989 (Box 10)
    - "Paris, City of Light," June 27-late, July, 1989 (Box 10)
    - "Prints by Richard Bosman: 1978-1988,", August 15-September 24, 1989 (Box 10)
      (Elvehjem Museum of Art, University of Wisconsin-Madison)
    - "Love Among the Gods,", August 9-September 10, 1989 (Box 10)
    - "Sun Pictures in Scotland,", September 15-October 29, 1989 (Box 10)
    - "Henri de Toulouse-Lautrec: Prints from the Permanent Collection,", September 15-October 29, 1989 (Box 10)
    - "Ansel Adams Photographs,", September 15-October 29, 1989 (Box 10)
    - "The Reflective Lens: 150 Years of Photography,", October 13-December 17, 1989 (Box 10)
    - "Images of the Native American West,", October 31-November 12, 1989 (Box 10)
    - "Middle Eastern Ceramics from University Collections,", November 11, 1989-January 15, 1990 (Box 10)
    - "Mainly Mozart," November 13-[December 23], 1989 (Box 10)
      (includes checklist within 1989 Michigan Mozartfest program)
    - "Style and Function,", November 14, 1989-January 15, 1990 (Box 10)
    - "Kiyochika: Artist of Meiji Japan,", January 19-March 11, 1990 (Box 10)
      (The Santa Barbara Museum of Art)
    - "Buddhist Mandala Painting,", February 21-23, 1990 (Box 10)
    - "A New Day Dawning: Early Cape Dorset Prints,", June 23-September 3, 1989 (Box 10)
    - "Twelve Artists from the German Democratic Republic,", February 9-March 25, 1990 (Box 10)
      (Busch-Reisinger Museum, Harvard University)
    - "Nineteenth-Century Realist Prints and Drawings,", March 16-April 15, 1990 (Box 10)
    - "Grounded: Sculpture on the Floor,", April 7-June 3, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 1990-1991
    - Schedule (Box 10)
    - "Metropolitan Life,", April 13-June 24, 1990 (Box 10)
    - "Indignity and Anger: Prints by Mexican Artists,", April 17-May 13, 1990 (Box 10)
    - "French Curves and Fine Habits: Rococo Textiles and Prints,", June 5-September 29, 1990 (Box 10)
    - "Art of the 1960s Part I and II," June 29-August 5, 1990 and August 10-[September 23], 1990 (Box 10)
      (in connection with History of Art 375: "Issues in American Art of the 1960s")
    - "Sondra Freckelton: Prints and Watercolors,", July 6-September 2, 1990 (Box 10)
    - "Bellows and Diebenkorn: Prints from the Doris Sloan Collection,", September 21-November 11, 1990 (Box 11)
      (includes object photographs)
    - "Lorna Simpson,", October 19-December 2, 1990 (Box 11)
      (University Art Museum, California State University, Long Beach)
    - "City and Country in French Prints, 1850-1900,", October 19-December 23, 1990 (Box 11)
    - "Rudolf L. Baumfeld Collection of Landscape Drawings and Prints,", November 9-December 23, 1990 (Box 11)
      (Grunwald Center for the Graphic Arts, University of California Los Angeles)
    - "Chinese New Year Posters,", January 12-March 3, 1991 (Box 11)
    - "Lessons from the East,", January 26-March 10, 1991 (Box 11)
    - "The Female Gaze,", February 9-March 24, 1991 (Box 11)
    - "Greece vs. Rome: The Search for the Classical Spirit,", March 16-April 28, 1991 (Box 11)
      (includes label copy and object photographs)
    - "Pudlo: Thirty Years of Drawing,", March 23-May 19, 1991 (Box 11)
      (National Gallery of Canada) (includes artist photographs)
    - "Travel Sketches by Albert Kahn,", March 30-June 9, 1991 (Box 11)
    - "Margarete Baum: Recent Paintings,", April 6-May 26, 1991 (Box 11)
    - "Photographs by Walker Evans,", May 11-July 7, 1991 (Box 11)
    - "Hidden Treasures,", June 8-August 18, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 1991-1992
    - Schedule (Box 11)
    - "The Art of Science,", June 15-September 29, 1991 (Box 11)
    - "Wide World of Whistler,", July 13-September 1, 1991 (Box 11)
    - "Art Words from the Brush" (Asian calligraphy), August 24-November 10, 1991 (Box 11)
    - "Rembrandt & the Bible: Etchings from the Feddersen Collection at the University of Notre Dame,", September 7-October 20, 1991; 2 folders (Box 11)
      (Snite Museum of Art, University of Notre Dame)
    - "I See America Dancing: Photographs by Barbara Morgan,", September 7-November 3, 1991 (Box 11)
    - "Photographs: Baldwin Lee,", November 2-December 22, 1991 (Box 11)
    - "Jasper Johns: Prints from the Kaufman Collection,", November 16, 1991-January 12, 1992 (Box 11)
    - "Tan Tee Chie: Recent Paintings, 1988-1991,", January 10-March 22, 1992 (Box 11)
    - "Paul Klee,", January 18-March 15, 1992 (Box 11)
    - "Picasso and Gris: Loans from the Carey Walker Foundation,", January 25, 1992-August 8, 1993 (Box 11)
      (includes label copy and opening event "An Evening with Pablo and his Friends")
    - "Comedy and the Artist's Eye,", February 1-March 15, 1992 (Box 11)
    - "The Pear: French Graphic Arts in the Golden Age of Caricature,", February 8-March 22, 1992; 2 folders (Box 11)
      (Mount Holyoke College Art Museum)
    - "(Choose an Old Master at the) Friends Acquisitions Event,", March 14, 1992 (Box 11)
    - "Realist Prints: Then and Now (1970-1990),", March 21-July 26, 1992 (Box 11)
    - "Story Quilts by Faith Ringgold,", March 21-May 17, 1992; 2 folders (Box 11)
      (includes label copy and visitor comment book)
    - "Couture and Fashion Accessories from the Sandy Schreier Collection," April 4-?, 1992 (Box 12)
    - "Joanne Leonard. Not Losing Her Memory: Stories in Photographs, Words and Collage,", April 4-June 7, 1992; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - "Sylvia Plimack Mangold: Works on Paper, 1968-1991,", April 11-June 7, 1992 (Box 12)
      (Davison Art Center, Wesleyan University and UMMA)
    - "Josef Hampl,", May 30-August 16, 1992 (Box 12)
    - "Beyond the Plane: Relief Paintings by Judith Rothschild,", June 27-August 16, 1992 (Box 12)
    - "Lithographs by Emil Weddige,", July 2-August 23, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 1992-1993
    - "Recent Gifts,", August 29-November 8, 1992 (Box 12)
    - "Tiffany Interiors from the H.O. Havemeyer House,", August 29, 1992-February 21, 1993 (Box 12)
    - "Old Master Drawings from the Collection of Joseph F. McCrindle,", September 5-October 25, 1992 (Box 12)
      (The Art Museum, Princeton University)
    - "Janice Gordon: Recent Constructions,", September 12-November 22, 1992 (Box 12)
    - "Vedute e Dettagli: The Photography of Carlo Naya,", September 19-November 29, 1992 (Box 12)
    - "The Invincible and Immortal Army: Warriors from Xian,", November 17, 1992-January 17, 1993 (Box 12)
    - "Four Treasures of the Chinese Scholar's Studio,", November 14, 1992-March 7, 1993 (Box 12)
    - "The Cultivated Image: Garden Photographs by Michael Kenna,", December 5, 1992-February 28, 1993 (Box 12)
    - Schedule, 1993 (Box 12)
    - "African Art from the Museum Collection: A Celebration,", February 13-August 1, 1993 (Box 12)
    - "In Focus: Guercino's Esther,", March 7-May 16, 1993 (Box 12)
    - "An Eighteenth-Century Moment: The Legacy of Charles Sawyer,", March 13-May 16, 1993 (Box 12)
    - "The Edwards Ledger Drawings: Art by Arapaho Warriors,", March 20-May 2, 1993 (Box 12)
    - "Creativity Within Constraints: The Art of Automobile Design,", May 23-August 15, 1993 (Box 12)
      (includes photograph and label copy)
    - "Artists Among Us: Michigan Narrative Quilts,", May 29-August 15, 1993 (Box 12)
  - 1993-1994
    - "William Scharf: Recent Paintings,", August 21-October 3, 1993 (Box 12)
    - "The Fair View: Representations of the World's Columbian Exhibition of 1893,", October 30-December 31, 1993; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - "From Mother Earth: Pueblo Pottery Along the Rio Grande,", September 4-November 28, 1993 (Box 12)
    - "German Expressionist Graphics from the Museum Collection,", September 11-December 5, 1993 (Box 12)
    - "Hannah Höch: Collages,", October 9-November 28, 1993 (Box 12)
    - "Socialist Realism: Twentieth-Century Paintings from the Soviet Union,", December 4, 1993-February 27, 1994 (Box 12)
    - "Japanese Woodblock Prints" (Clements Library), December 10, 1993 (Box 12)
    - "Larry Cressman: An Installation,", December 11, 1993-March 6, 1994 (Box 12)
    - "James Tissot: Prints from the Aldrich Collection,", January 15-March 6, 1994 (Box 13)
    - "Driven to Abstraction: Art of the Twentieth Century,", February 11-Mid-Summer 1994 (Box 13)
    - "Paintings by Mark Rothko: 1945-1969,", March 5-May 8, 1994 (Box 13)
    - "Cubism and its Legacy,", March 12-May 29, 1994 (Box 13)
    - "Photographs by Howard Bond (Landscape Images from the Greek Islands and the Great Sand Dunes National Monument, Colorado),", March 19-June 12, 1994 (Box 13)
    - "Whistler: Prosaic Views, Poetic Vision. Works on Paper from the University of Michigan Museum of Art,", March 26-May 22, 1994; 2 folders (Box 13)
      (includes photograph and press kit)
    - "The Return to Figuration,", May 20-September 4, 1994 (Box 13)
    - "Reflections of the Everyday World: Seventeenth-Century Dutch Prints,", June 10-August 21, 1994 (Box 13)
  - 1994-1995
    - "Transition and Transformation: African Art of the In-Between,", September 1994-June 1995 (Box 13)
    - "The Jade Studio: Masterpieces of Ming and Qing Painting from the Wong Nan-P'ing Collection,", September 10-November 20, 1994 (Box 13)
      (Yale University Art Gallery)
    - "Beyond Empire: Artistic Expressions of Byzantium,", September 17-October 30, 1994 (Box 13)
    - "Isamu Noguchi: Exploration and Collaboration,", September 24-November 13, 1994 (Box 13)
    - "John Stephenson: After the Fire, A Retrospective,", November 5, 1994-January 15, 1995 (Box 13)
    - "Staffs of Life: African Rods, Staffs and Sceptres from the Coudron Collection,", December 3, 1994-February 26, 1995 (Box 13)
    - "Joseph Beuys: Drawings, Objects and Prints,", January 14-March 5, 1995; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - "Divine Illuminations: Devotional Books of the Middle Ages,", February 4-March 26, 1995 (Box 13)
    - "Modern Japanese Ceramics," February 17-?, 1995 (Box 13)
    - "What Is a Portrait? Depictions of Women from the Eighteenth through the Twentieth Centuries,", March 3-April 30, 1995 (Box 13)
    - "Labor and Leisure: French Prints from the Latter Half of the Nineteenth Century,", March 11-May 14, 1995 (Box 13)
    - "In Focus: Kai Ch'i,", April 8-June 4, 1995 (Box 13)
    - "Docents' Choice: Celebrating Twenty Years of Museum Teaching,", June 3-October 1, 1995 (Box 13)
    - "From Ansel Adams to Andy Warhol: Portraits and Self-Portraits,", March 25-May 21, 1995 (Box 13)
    - "Art In Bloom,", June 24-August 6, 1995 (Box 13)
    - "The Allure of the Nude,", June 17-August 20, 1995 (Box 13)
  - 1995-1996
    - "Edda Renouf: Paintings, Drawings and Prints,", August 19-November 15, 1995 (Box 13)
    - "Adriaen van Ostade: Etchings of Peasant Life in Holland's Golden Age,", September 2-October 15, 1995 (Box 13)
      (Georgia Museum of Art, University of Georgia)
    - "Japanese Gallery Opening Celebration,", October 1, 1995 (Box 13)